Finding Aid for the Will Connell Papers LSC.0893
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Part Three, The following photographs are unmounted and are 35.1 × 27.7cm. (14 × 11) unless otherwise noted.; Compiled by Kayla Landesman and Hilda Bohem.
  - 3. What little girl stars are made of, Make-up, wig, etc., 1938. (Box 37)
  - 4. Connell adjusting lights, n.d.; (24.5 × 19.5c.m.). (Box 37)
  - 5. Humerous self(?) - portrait, n.d.; (34 × 27cm.). (Box 37)
  - 6. Hosiery advertisement: Model's legs in slippers, garters and hosiery, 1932.; (Trick effect). (Box 37)
  - 7. Close-up of model's foot, 1938. (Box 37)
  - 8. Insignia for the club, 1936.; Trick photography (45 × 35cm.). (Box 37)
  - 9. Three light bulbs, 1930.; Trick effect. (Box 37)
  - 10-11. Eyeglasses, 1929-1935.; Various special effects. (Box 37)
  - 12-13. Champagne glasses, 1930-31.; Various special effects. (Box 37)
  - 14-15. Chevrolet montages, 1938.; (Mounted, 38 × 44cm.). (Box 37)
  - 16. Open ice-box with drop-tray added. (Box 37)
- Photos exhibited in LACMA's Masters of Star-light, December 1987-February 1988
  Items borrowed from UCLA Library Department of Special Collections by Will Connell, Jr., 1979.
  - Al Jolson
    - Portrait of Jolson smoking a cigarette, 1935.; (31 × 24cm., 43 × 36cm. and 51 × 41cm.). (Box 38)
  - Chorus Line
    - Chorus girls smoking on movie set, ca. 1937.; (39 × 24cm., 46 × 36cm. and 51 × 41cm.). (Box 38)
  - Still-Man
    - Trick photograph of miniature photographer and equipment dodging the feet of giants., ca. 1936.; (34 × 27cm., 46 × 36cm. and 51 × 41cm.). (Box 38)
      Published: in Pictures, p.61. Available in Department of Special Collections [*TR 16.8 C762i].
  - A Study in Rain--Downtown
    - [No further description available]., ca. 1925.; (35 × 28cm. (unmatted) and 51 × 41cm.). (Box 38)
      Date provided by motion picture advertisement in image.
  - Ginger Rogers
    - Profile portrait., 1932.; 29 × 24cm., 46 × 36cm. and 51 × 41cm. (Box 38)
      Image originally in Part 1, Box 1.
  - George Arlis
    - Portrait of Arlis on movie set., 1932.; Titled on verso of image. 21 × 24cm., 46 × 36cm. and 51 × 41cm. (Box 38)
  - Myrna Loy
    - Three-quarters profile of seated actress., 1932.; 29 × 24cm., 46 × 36cm. and 51 × 41cm. (Box 38)
  - Walt Disney
    - Image of Mickey Mouse (taken from Disney's drawing board) is superimposed over portrait of Disney., ca. 1935.; 41 × 34cm., 46 × 36cm. and 51 × 41cm. (Box 38)
  - Cutting
    - Caption: Editing, 1933.; 30 × 24cm., 43 × 36cm. and 51 × 41cm. (Box 38)
      Published in Pictures, p.91. Available in Department of Special Collections [*TR 16.8 C762i].
  - Fashion montage, 1937. (Box 38)
    Formerly in Box 16, no.59.
    Returned from U/MD.
  - Trumpet Superimposed over another instrument. (Box 38)
    Formerly in Box 16, no.24.
  - Chevrolet montage., 1 item. (Box 38)
    Formerly in Box 16.
- Part 2, The following photographs are unmounted and of various sizes, chiefly 20 × 25.5cm. (8 × 10) unless otherwise noted.; Most photographs are not individually identified as in Part 1, however Grace Connell (Mrs. Will Connell) identified some of the groups of photographs and transparencies. No dates are given; there are multiple duplicates.
  Cataloged by Kayla Landesman and typed by Alva Stevenson.
  - Miscellaneous photographs., 1926-28 (Box 39)
    - Miniature portraits, identified on mount or verso., Mainly mounted (28 × 20.5cm.). 28 items. (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Hollyhock House, Barnsdall Park, Los Angeles, n.d.; Unmounted, 20 × 25cm. 31 items. (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Photographs of paintings by Maynard Dixon and Paul Sample., Unmounted, 20 × 25cm. 10 items. (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Circus views, Ringling Brothers, Los Angeles, n.d.; Unmounted, 19.5 × 25cm. (Box 39, Folder 4-5)
      - [No further description available]., 30 items. (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - [No further description available]., 30 items. (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Portraits, some identified., 35 photos. (Box 39, Folder 6)
      Includes the following:
      - Shackleford. (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - Bill Conselman. (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - Barse Miller. (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - Jose Rodriguez. (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - Bertha and Raymond Griffith. (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - Don Herold. (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - A.B. MacCallister. (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - Ken Alexander. (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - Merle Armitage. (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - Phil Townsend Hanna. (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - Will Connell. (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - Grace Connell. (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Industrial Views., Includes the following: Woodcutters, Cal Ship, Lockheed-Douglas, Rheem, Kobe, Barr Lumber, Ramo Wooldridge, Textile, and Electric Motor. (Box 40)
    - [No further description available]., 22 photos. (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - [No further description available]., 22 photos. (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - [No further description available]., 22 photos. (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - [No further description available]., 22 photos. (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - [No further description available]., 22 photos. (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - [No further description available]., 22 photos. (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Views., Includes the following: Beckman, TWA, Lockheed, McCullock (Motor), Kaiser, Hunt Foods, American Can, and Electroweld. (Box 40, Folder 7-12)
    - [No further description available]., 22 photos. (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - [No further description available]., 22 photos. (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - [No further description available]., 22 photos. (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - [No further description available]., 27 photos. (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - [No further description available]., 27 photos. (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Industrial Views
    - Los Angeles, Hollywood, Pasadena, Airfield., 30 photos. (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Fairchild Aerial Surveys., 10 photos. (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Hughes Tool, Texas., 22 photos. (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Hughes Tool, Texas., 22 photos. (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Hughes Aircraft., 30 photos. (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Sylvester (Vard)., 22 photos. (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Sylvester (Vard)., 22 photos. (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Kobe Incorporated., 20 photos. (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Kobe Incorporated., 20 photos. (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Kobe Incorporated., 21 photos. (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Industrial (2nd employees book)., 27 photos. (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - California Missions and Miscellaneous Views
    - Monterey., 9 photos. (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Pala., 11 photos. (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Plaza Church, Los Angeles., 1 photo. (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - La Purisima Concepcion., 6 photos. (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - San Antonio de Padua., 12 photos. (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - San Carlos Borromeo Carmel., 17 photos. (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - San Buena Ventura., 2 photos. (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - San Diego de Alcala., 9 photos. (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - San Fernando., 10 photos. (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - San Francisco de Asis (Dolores)., 8 photos. (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - San Gabriel., 14 photos. (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - San Jose., 2 photos. (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - San Juan Bautista., 12 photos. (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - San Juan Capistrano., 12 photos. (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - San Luis Obispo., 6 photos. (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - San Luis Rey., 23 photos. (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - San Miguel., 25 photos. (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Santa Barbara., 13 photos. (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Santa Clara., 2 photos. (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - Santa Cruz., 2 photos. (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - Santa Ynez., 13 photos. (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - Soledad., 1 photo. (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous views., 42 photos. (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous views including Lompoc Flower Seed Farm., 42 photos. (Box 42, Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous views including USO views., 40 photos. (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Advertising, and industrial, and miscellaneous views. (Box 43)
    - Miscellaneous views, includes beekeeping and bowling., 94 photos. (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Farmer's Market and Park La Brea, Los Angeles., 27 photos. (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Ads - Sneezes., 24 photos. (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Ads - Sneezes., 22 photos. (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Ads - Purex., 21 photos. (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Animals., 6 photos. (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Dogs., 12 photos. (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Cats., 45 photos. (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Cats and other animals., 50 photos. (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Architecture. Del Norte Elementary School., 24 photos. (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Architecture. Del Norte Elementary School., 20 photos. (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Industrial views., 4 × 5 Kodachrome transparencies and black and white prints. Arranged in groups, 41 envelopes. 501 items. (Box 44)
    Includes:
    - Hughes Tool. (Box 44)
    - Kaiser Steel. (Box 44)
    - Lockheed. (Box 44)
    - Fortune Articles. (Box 44)
    - [Miscellaneous]. (Box 44)
      Most of these are represented in the black and white prints.
  - Photographs by other photographers (some identified) of Will Connell and his Art Center Photo class; Miscellaneous industrial photos. (Box 45)
    - Photos by Edward Painter McMortry., 20 photos. (Box 45, Folder 1)
      (See Collection folder for notes on these images)
    - Photos of Connell and his class., 26 items. (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Photos of Connell and his class, some by Connell., 26 items. (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Photos of Connell and his class., 26 photos. (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Photos of Connell and his class., 26 photos. (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Photos of Connell and his class., 26 photos. (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Photos of Connell and his class., 26 photos. (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Photos of Connell and his class., 24 photos. (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Adel (Precision Industrial Devices)., 22 photos. (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Adel (Precision Industrial Devices)., 22 photos. (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Adel (Precision Industrial Devices)., 19 photos. (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous color prints and transparencies, mostly advertising. (Box 46)
    - Color prints, some black and white., 29 photos. (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Color prints., 39 photos. (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Color prints., 30 photos. (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Color transparencies and negatives. A few photos included., 46 items. (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Advertising Photographs
    - Food., 41 photographs (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Food., 50 photographs. (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Merchandise., 50 photographs, 2 negatives. (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Merchandise., 44 photographs. (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Merchandise., 54 photographs. (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Stores: interior and exterior., 35 photographs. (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Homes. (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Homes: Los Altos home of Frank Taylor and Altadena home by Lloyd Wright., 55 photos. (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Advertisements: Movie Stars, etc., The movie photos include: Dale Evans, Maxy Rosenblum, Myrna Loy, Joan Crawford, John Garfield, Victor McLaughlin, and Tom Landon.
    - [No further description available]., 31 photos. (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - [No further description available]., 34 photos. (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - [No further description available]., 46 photos. (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - [No further description available]., 44 photos. (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - [No further description available]., 34 photos. (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - [No further description available]., 36 photos. (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - [No further description available]., 36 photos. (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous done for Fortune Magazine, Including: Farmers Market, Santa Claus, Gobel, WACs, Lompoc flowers, Army during the war, Oil (Richfield mostly), Nursery flowers and plants, and Home interiors.
    - [No further description available]., 33 photos. (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - [No further description available]., 35 photos. (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - [No further description available]., 26 photos. (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - [No further description available]., 24 photos. (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - [No further description available]., 26 photos. (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - [No further description available]., 26 photos. (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - [No further description available]., 26 photos. (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - [No further description available]., 26 photos. (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - [No further description available]., 26 photos. (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Large Kodachrome (transparencies), 1940s.; 14 mounted, many signed on the mount and 7 unmounted. (Box 50)
  - Industrial Photos, etc.
    - Orange; farming; Palm Springs; San Bernadino; lumber., 38 photos. (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Big Bear Boy's Camp; San Francisco., 15 photos. (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Nutralite., 30 photos. (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Nutralite., 33 photos. (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Nutralite., 30 photos. (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Fluor Corporation., 20 photos. (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Fluor Corporation., 22 photos. (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Fluor Corporation., 22 photos. (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Nursery School
    - Book., 1 item. (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Rough dummy, copy and captions for proposed but unpublished book on Nursery Schools, World War II., Typescript and photos. (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - [No further description available]., 26 photos. (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - [No further description available]., 57 small photos. (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - [No further description available]., 25 photos. (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Color Transparencies, Mostly Mounted
    - Coachella., 5 photos. (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Birds., 4 photos. (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Death Valley., 24 photos. (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Delphiniums., 9 photos. (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Flowers., 6 photos. (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Halloween Cat., 2 photos. (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Richfield., 6 photos. (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Santa Inez Valley., 9 photos. (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Teen-agers., 2 photos. (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Tehachapi., 25 photos. (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous., 24 photos. (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous., 23 photos. (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Ektachromes, miscellaneous., 10 photos. (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Ektachromes., Unmounted, 67 photos. (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Views of the Southwest
    - Miscellaneous landscapes., 12 photos. (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Palos Verde, Balboa, San Pedro, Ventura, Laguna., 29 photos. (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Laguna, Santa Monica, Balboa., 24 photos. (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Newport Beach, Catalina., 26 photos. (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Palos Verde, Cajon Pass, Hollywood., 23 photos (also 22 5 × 7). (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - High Sierras, Sequoia, Miscellaneous mountains and trees., 29 photos. (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - High Sierras, Desert, Death Valley., 39 photos. (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - High Sierras, San Gabriel Mountains., 26 photos. (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Red Rock Canyon, Mojave, Sierras., 28 photos. (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Taos and Santa Fe., 19 photos. (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - San Francisco and Palo Alto., 35 photos. (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Oil; Pomona College
    - Mock-up for book on oil. (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Oil., 20 photos. (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Oil., 22 photos. (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Oil., 22 items. (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Pomona College., 26 photos. (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Pomona College., 30 photos. (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Pomona College., 26 photos. (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Pomona College, 25 photos. (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Color Transparencies
    - Grapes. (Mounted Kodachrome)., 19 photos. (Box 56, Folder 1)
      Sketches of grapes in Ephemera, box 21.
    - Grapes., (Mounted Kodachrome) 19 photos. (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Color experiments., (X color) 26 photos. (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - 4 × 5 color in groups in envelopes., 13 envelopes. (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - 4 × 5 color in groups in envelopes., 13 envelopes. (Box 56, Folder 5)
      (folders 4 and 5 are identified as models, grapes, flowers, movies, Colliers, etc.)
  - Nutralite., 29 photos. (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Nutralite., 34 photos. (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Nutralite., 30 photos. (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Nutralite., 30 photos. (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Nutralite., 34 photos. (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Nutralite., 32 photos. (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Nutralite., 36 photos. (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Ekoware., 33 photos. (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Glass and other commercial., 55 small photos, various sizes. (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous unidentified portraits., 56 photos of which 24 are various small sizes. (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Big Bear Boys' Camp., 78 photos, dry mounted back-to-back to make the leaves of a book (not bound). (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Big Bear Boys' Camp., 35 photos. (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Tamarack Girls' Camp., 36 photos. (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Proofs of Big Bear Boys' Camp and Tamarack Girls' Camp photos. (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence and ephemera including newspaper clippings and pamphlets relating to Connell's work and publications, typescripts of speeches(?) and ideas. (Box 59)
  - 3-D experimental photographs., Black and white and color, some mounted. 19 photos. (Box 60)
  - Hughes Aircraft., 248 photos. (Box 60)
  - Kaiser Steel., 4 photos. (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Group portrait, includes Will Connell., 2 photographs. (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Wine industry, primarily Wente Brothers., 33 photos. (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - The Barge operations of the Bar Lumber Company. Photos by Will Connell, text by Grace Connell., 1 spiral-bound book. (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - The Barge operations... miniature mock-up book. (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Will Connell. Miscellaneous portrait and advertisemnts photograph book., 1 spiral-bound book. (Box 61, Folder 6)
- Papers, 1928-1961. (Box 61)
  - Periodicals. (Box 62, Box 63)
  - Photographs and album. (Box 64)
  - Photograph album. (Box 65)
  - Photographs and album (Includes portrait of Lloyd Wright and wife Helen, also one of Jake Zeitlin). (Box 66)
  - 1st.-6th. Annual of advertising art in the U.S. (Box 67)
  - 7th.-11th. Annual of advertising art in the U.S. (Box 68)
  - 12th.-16th. Annual of advertising art in the U.S. (Box 69)
  - 17th.-20th. Annual of advertising art in the U.S. (Box 70)
  - 21st.-25th. Annual of advertising art in the U.S. (Box 71)
  - 26th.-29th. Annual of advertising art in the U.S. (Box 72)
  - 30th.-33rd. Annual of advertising art in the U.S. (Box 73)
  - Periodicals. (Box 74)
  - Articles
    - Correspondence:, 1930-1931, 1937 and 1959. (Box 75)
    - Notes. (Box 75)
    - Research material. (Box 75)
  - Correspondence, 1957-1961
    - ASMP material. (Box 76)
    - Printed material. (Box 76)
  - Photography manuals., Printed material. (Box 77)
  - Prints. (Box 78, Box 79)
  - Printed material. (Box 80, Box 81, Box 82)
  - Print blocks. (Box 83, Box 84)
  - Printed material, sketches, wood blocks. (Box 85)
  - Printed material. (Box 86, Box 87)
  - Work-up no.1 Missions of California. (Box 88)
  - Work-up no.2 Missions of California. (Box 88)
  - Grace Brown Christmas cards. (Box 88)
  - Color slides of Lockheed., 3 × 5. (Box 89)
  - Color transparencies. (Box 89)
  - Printed material. (Box 90)
  - Negatives. (Box 91, Box 92)
  - Negatives - nursery flowers etc. (Box 93)
  - Negatives - Kobe. (Box 94)
  - Negatives - Palomar, etc. (Box 95)
  - Negatives - Jim Real, Hughes Air. (Box 96)
  - Hughes Air file, Real, 1-972. (Box 97)
  - Hughes Air file, 973-, & Noyes. (Box 98)
  - Hughes Air. (Box 99)
  - Nutrilite file, 1-514, Life (Box 100)
  - Nutrilite file, 515 - M & C portraits of REJ. (Box 101)
  - Companion Journal, Sep, Country, Century (Box 102)
  - Scrapbooks of pages from Life magazine on each of the following subjects: Photography, electronics, silk, jets & rockets, education and cars. (Box 103)
  - Scrapbooks of pages from Life magazine on each of the following subjects: Otto Hagel, Hansel Mieth, Bob (Robert) Capa, Los Angeles, railroads and automobiles, BG Ralph Coane, Loomis Dean, (Leonard) McCombe, and (Margaret) Bourke-White. (Box 104)
  - Scrapbooks of pages from Life magazine on each of the following subjects: Feininger, Cartier-Bresson, Eyeoman Haas, Nina Leen, Wallace Kirkland, Englund and Eisenstadt. (Box 105)
  - Scrapbooks of pages from Life magazine on each of the following subjects: Lisa Larsen, Gordon Parks, Carl Mydans, Gjon Mili, Duncan, and Dmitri Kessel. (Box 106)
  - Scrapbooks of pages from Life magazine on each of the following subjects: Publicity & ads, astronomics - maps & calendars, weather, oil, stage - Los Angeles and Adams. (Box 107)
  - Los Angeles Times rotogravure section., 1930. (Box 108)
  - Tear sheets. (Box 108)
  - Printed material. (Box 108)
  - Scrapbooks of pages from Life magazine on each of the following subjects: U.S. states and cities. (Box 109)
    - Halsman war photographs. (Box 109)
    - Elisofon U.S. general - flags, symbols etc. (Box 109)
    - U.S. - face of America. (Box 109)
  - Printed material. (Box 110)
  - Promotion pieces and ads. (Box 111)
  - Printed material - advertising. (Box 112)
  - Tool shop catalogs and poster book. (Box 113)
  - Tear sheets. (Box 114, Box 115)
  - Proof sheets. (Box 116)
  - Tear sheets. (Box 117)
  - Clippings. (Box 118)
  - Printed material. (Box 119)
  - Engraving plates. (Box 120)
  - Clippings. (Box 121)
  - 100 best posters, 1935. (Box 121)
  - Commercial art, vol.10. (Box 121)
  - Printed material. (Box 122)
  - Proofs. (Box 122)
  - Line drawings by Geretz. (Box 122)
  - Printed material. (Box 123)
  - Photos. (Box 123)
  - Awards from the 1st., 3rd. and 5th. Annual Exhibition of Advertising Art of the Art Directors Club of Los Angeles, 1945, 1947 & 1949.; (Poster box). (Box 124)
- Boxes 149-151 are stored in the nitrate vaults in Hollywood. (Box 149, Box 150, Box 151)
- Photogram-Nite Glass Cut-Outs, 6 negatives for 3-D photos and 2 3-D glass slides. (Box 152)
- Proofs and Negatives
  - Abbott Kimball / Brock's
    - Safety negatives. (Box 138)
  - Ack Briggs
    - Safety negatives. (Box 143)
  - ADEL (negative no.1-135)
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 127)
  - ADEL (negative no.136- )
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 128)
  - Adohr
    - Glass negatives. (Box 131)
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 149)
  - American Air R & R
    - Safety negatives. (Box 135)
  - Anabolic Food Products Incorporated (Including 1 Colour Transparency)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 138)
  - Arden Dairy
    - Glass negatives. (Box 142)
  - Arrowhead Puritas
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 149)
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
  - Arrowhead Water
    - Glass negatives. (Box 126)
  - Art Directors
    - Safety negatives. (Box 138)
  - Assorted Heads
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 151)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 146)
  - Axelson Eng
    - Glass negatives. (Box 131)
  - Axelson Gage
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
  - Axelson Pump
    - Glass negatives. (Box 131 and 136)
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 150)
  - Axelson Pumps
    - Glass negatives. (Box 136)
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 150)
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
  - B & H Norris Standing
    - Safety negatives. (Box 135)
  - Baby Swain / ADA / Oppenheim
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 151)
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 143)
  - Barse Miller
    - Glass negatives. (Box 144)
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 150)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 143)
  - BBD & O Clary
    - Safety negatives. (Box 138)
  - Beaumont Newhall
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 146)
  - Bechtel - McCone
    - Safety negatives. (Box 134)
  - Bent Phillips
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 151)
  - Bethlehem Steel
    - Safety negatives. (Box 138)
  - BH & G - Swim, 1959
    - Safety negatives. (Box 135 and 137)
  - BH & G - George Gobel
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 137)
  - BH & G Santa's Village
    - Safety negatives. (Box 135)
  - BH & G Spirit April
    - Glass negatives. (Box 136)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 137)
  - Bill Jenney & Jr.
    - Safety negatives. (Box 146)
  - Black & White lantern slide (1)